<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>/oliviahuang.netlify.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/oliviahuang.netlify.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Gross for Top Movies</title>
      <link>/oliviahuang.netlify.com/cope/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/oliviahuang.netlify.com/cope/</guid>
      <description>Description of Project For my Information Design course, I created a data visualization based on a topic of my choice. I decided to explore film gross data from Box Office Mojo.
Result From working on this project, I was able to successfully capture a cinematic and regal tone through my visual representation of the data, creating a compelling visualization for the audience. I accurately and clearly depicted film profit trends and patterns</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unsupervised Machine Learning Project</title>
      <link>/oliviahuang.netlify.com/360pro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/oliviahuang.netlify.com/360pro/</guid>
      <description>Description of Project In my Fraud Analytics course, my team and I performed a detailed analysis of &amp;lsquo;New York City Property Tax Valuation Data&amp;rsquo; and identified potential fraudulent records from the data set using unsupervised machine learning methods.
Project Goal Our objective was to use machine learning algorthims, such as Autoencoder and Heuristic Algorithms, and calculate a fraud score for each of the New York Property data records to analyze anomalies for potential fraud detection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geospatial Analysis of Los Angeles County Homelessness</title>
      <link>/oliviahuang.netlify.com/tedx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/oliviahuang.netlify.com/tedx/</guid>
      <description>Description of Project This was the Capstone project for my Statistical Computing and Data Visualization Course at USC Marshall, in which we worked for Los Angeles County. My key roles were cleaning and analyzing data on LA County homeless count, specifically looking at the top 10 homeless communities and their ratio of unsheltered to sheltered homeless person. Second, I crafted visualizations and a formal presentation to map our group results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>